Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory--Advisory Council, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- M (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 47)
- M (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 48)
- Mann Library, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- Media Services, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- Microbiology, Section of, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Migrants, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- Miner Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Minorities, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Minority Graduate Student & Faculty Recruitment, Committee to Monitor, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Minority Resources Development Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Minority Resources Development Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- N (General Correspondence), 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of--CSRS Review, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of--CSRS Review, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Northeast Center for Agricultural Health & Safety, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Northeast Cooperative Council, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Northeast Dairy Compact, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Northeast Dairy Foods Research Center (Dave Barbano, Director), 1991 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- NY Labor Study, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- NY Seed Improvement Cooperative, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Audit Report, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Director's Office, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Entomology Department, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Food, Science, & Technology, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Horticultural Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Memorandum of Agreement--Fruit Testing Association & Geneva, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva--Plant Pathology Department, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- NYS Environmental Conservation, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- NYS Fair, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- NYS Green Council, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- NYS Rural Affairs, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- NYS Rural Safety Council, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- NYS Soil Conservation Service/Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- NYS Soil Conservation Service/Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- NYS Soil Conservation Service/Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- O (General Correspondence), 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 38)
- P (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- PACNYS (Pesticide Association of NYS), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Peace Studies Program, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Personal Enterprise Program (PEP), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 42)
- Personal Enterprise Program (PEP), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Personal Enterprise Program (PEP), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Personal Enterprise Program (PEP), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Pesticide Use on Campus, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Physiology, Dept. & Section of, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Pimentel, David Handbook (Pesticides), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Pimentel, David Handbook (Pesticides), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Planning (John Wiesenfeld, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Planning (John Wiesenfeld, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Plant Biology, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Plant Biology, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Plant Breeding & Biometry, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Pomology (Ithaca & Geneva), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Population & Development Program (International Population Program), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Poultry & Avian Sciences, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Poultry Research Facilities, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Poultry Science Reorganization, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Provost, Senior (Robert Barker), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Provost, Senior (Robert Barker), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Provost (Malden Nesheim), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Provost (Malden Nesheim), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Provost (Malden Nesheim), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs, Office of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Lael C. Carter, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Lael C. Carter, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Lael C. Carter, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs, Office of (Richard Ramin, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Presidential Scholars, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Pro-Fac Cooperative, Inc., 1991 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Q (General Correspondence), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- R (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Research, Office for, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Research, Office for (David Brown, Associate Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Research, Office for (Brian Chabot, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Research, Office for (Brian Chabot, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Reseach & Advanced Studies (Norm Scott,, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Reseach & Advanced Studies (Norm Scott,, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Residency Status, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Retirement, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Rich, Thomas & Helen Food & Nutrition Laboratory, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- Risk Management & Insurance (George Meeker), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 36)
- Rural Schools Program, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 38)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 39)
- Russia--Scholar Exchange Program, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 40)
- S (General Correspondence), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Science, Technology, & Society, Program on, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Science & Technology Studies, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 43)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 44)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 45)
- Sea Grant Institute--Board of Governors, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 46)
- Senators, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 47)
- Shackelton Point, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 48)
- Shoals Marine Laboratory (John Barrett Heiser), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 49)
- Shoals Marine Laboratory (John Barrett Heiser), 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 50)
- Soil, Crop, & Atmospheric Sciences, Dept. of, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 51)
- Soviet & East European Studies Program, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 52)
- Special Initiatives, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Sponsored Programs (T. Rogers), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Staff Development & Recruitment, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Statutory College Affairs (Nathan Fawcett, Director), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Students, Dean of, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Sustainable Agriculture, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- T (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Tetra-Pak Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Title V (Rural Development), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Tompkins County Soil Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Toxic Chemicals Laboratory, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Turfgrass Facility Design, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- U (General Correspondence), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Uganda Project, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Uihlein Farm, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- United Way, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- University Council, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- University Coucil, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- University Counsel, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- University Relations (John Burness, Vice President), 1990 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- University Relations (Henrick N. Dullea, Vice President), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- USDA, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- V (General Correspondence), 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Vice President, Senior (James Morley, Jr.), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Vice President & Treasurer, Office of (Fred Rogers), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Visiting Committee (in re: diversity), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- W (General Correspondence), 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Waste Management Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Waste Management Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Watershed Agricultural Program--NYC, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Watershed Agricultural Program--NYC, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Watershed Agricultural Program--NYC, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Willsboro Health Center, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Wing, Kenneth, Associate Dean, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Winrock International Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Y (General Correspondence), 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Z (General Correspondence), 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- A (General Correspondence), 1992-1994 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Academic Programs & Campus Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Academic Programs & Campus Affairs (George Conneman, Associate Dean), 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Academic Programs & Campus Affairs (Elizabeth Oltenacu, Associate Director), 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Administrative Services, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Administrative Services, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- Admissions, 1990-1994 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- Admissions & Financial Aid (Susan Murphy, Dean), 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Admissions Structure, Provost's Committee on, 1981-1993 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Admissions Structure, Provost's Committee on, 1981-1993 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Affirmative Action Plan, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, Dept. of--Letters in re cancellation of ABEN 110 & 132, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Agricultural Library, Association of National, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Library, Association of National, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Library, Association of National, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Protection Act (Right to Farm Bill), 1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Agricultural Research Inititative, National, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Agriculture, Proposal on Experimentation & Advance of Science in, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- AgSat--Board of Directors' Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- AgSat--Board of Directors' Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Agway, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Alexander von Humboldt Foundation Award, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Alpha Gamma Rho, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Alpha Zeta, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Alumni Association (John C. Sterling), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- American Indian Agriculture Project, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- American Indian Program, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- American Indian Program, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- American Indian Program--Akwe:kon Press Quarterly Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- American Indian Program--Mediation, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- American Indian Program--Mediation, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- American Indian Program (Barbara Abrams, Interim Director), 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- American People Ambassador Program, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Animal Science, Dept. of--Memo of Agreement with Brasil, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Animal Science, Dept. of--Memo of Agreement with University of Milan, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Arnot Forest, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Asia/Cornell Relationships, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Asia (Southeast) Program, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Asia (Southeast) Program, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 33)
- ATANY (Association of Teachers of Agriculture of New York, Inc.), 1992 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Athletics Department, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Athletics--Admissions Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 36)
- Audit Report--CALS, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- B (General Correspondence), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 39)
- Biochemistry, Molecular & Cell Biology, Section of, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 40)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Biometrics Unit, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 42)
- Biometrics Unit, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 43)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 44)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 45)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 46)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 47)
- Burns, Guy, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 48)
- bST, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 49)
- C (General Correspondence), 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 50)
- CARDI (Community & Rural Development Institute), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 51)
- CARDI (Community & Rural Development Institute), 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 52)
- Career Club, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 53)
- Career Development, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 54)
- Carter, Harvey (Professor of Natural Resources), 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture, & Development), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture, & Development), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- CIIFAD--Correspondence, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- CIIFAD--External Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- CIT (Cornell Information Technologies), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- CIT (Cornell Information Technologies), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- CIT (Cornell Information Technologies), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- CIT--Instructional Technologies Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Coffman, W. Ronnie (Associate Dean for Research and Director of NYS Agricultural Experiment Station), 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Cohn Farm, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Communication, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Congress Members, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Controller, Office of, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Cooperative Extension, Office of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Cooperative Extension, Office of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Cooperative Extension, Office of (Lucinda Noble, Director), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Cooperative Extension, Office of (Lucinda Noble, Director), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Extension, Office of (R. David Smith, Associate Director, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Cornell Abroad, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Cornell Plantations, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Cornell Plantations--Personnel, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- County Law 224, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Dairy Manure Management, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Dairy Markets & Policy (Andrew Novakovic, Director), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Dean, Associate (William Boldt), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Dean's Message & Budget Request, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Dean's Message & Budget Request, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Dean's Message & Budget Request, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Decker, Dan (NY Ag Experiment Station & Office for Research), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Development Office (Dave Dunlop, Director of Capital Projects), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Dyson, John (Donor), 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- E (General Correspondence), 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 35)
- East Asia Program, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Eastern European Cornell Exchange, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 37)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Ecology & Systematics / Ornithology Lab--Memo of Understanding, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- Education, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 40)
- Education, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 41)
- Education, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Education, Dept. of--Strategic Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Educating Leaders of Tomorrow--Task Force on, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- Empire Farm Days, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Entomology, Ad hoc Committee on Insect Biology, Science, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 47)
- Entrepreneur of the Year, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 48)
- Environment, Center for the, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Environment, Center for the, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Environment, Center for the--Director, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 51)
- EPA (Environmental Protection Agency), 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 52)
- European Studies, Institute for, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 53)
- Executive Policy Review Group, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 54)
- EYH Program (Expanding Your Horizons), 1993-1995 (Box 51, Folder 55)
- F (General Correspondence), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Facilities & Business Operations (Harold Craft, Jr, Vice President), 1992 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Facilities Planning & Construction (Paul Griffen, Vice President), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Facilities, Statutory Office for Capital, 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Facilities, Statutory Office for Capital, 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Faculty, Dean of, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Farm Services, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Farming Alternatives, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- FFA, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Finance & Business Office, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Food Safety Initiative, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Food Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Food Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Food Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Food Science--Master of Engineering Degree, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Food Science--Strategic Plan, 1991-1995 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Food Science--Strategic Plan, 1991-1995 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Food Science, Institute of, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Food Science, Institute of--Advisory Council, 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- 4-H, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Forensics, Dept. of, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Frosty Hill Fellowships, 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Fruit & Vegetable Science, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- G (General Correspondence), 1992-1995 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Gamma Sigma Delta, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Gamma Sigma Delta--Award for Distinguished Service to Agriculture (Jan Kennedy Olsen), 1993 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Genetics & Development, Section of, 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Geneva Property, 1992-1995 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Golf Course Management Program--Robert Trent Jones, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Robert Barlow), 1993 (Box 52, Folder 31)
- Graduate School, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- Graduate School--Study Committee on, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- H (General Correspondence), 1990-1994 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Hatfield Fellows, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- Hispanic American Studies Program, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- Hoff, John (Ag International), 1980-1992 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- Hubert Humphrey Fellowships, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- Hudson Valley Laboratory, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 39)
- Human Relations (Joycelyn Hart, Associate Vice President), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 40)
- Human Resource Development Council, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 41)
- Human Resource Development Council, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Hungary, Czechoslovakia, & Cornell Relations, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 43)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 44)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 45)
- Information Technologies (Stuart Lynn), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 46)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 47)
- IPM--Grower Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 48)
- International Agriculture, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 49)
- International Agriculture, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 50)
- International Agriculture, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 51)
- International Memoranda of Agreement, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 52)
- International Memoranda of Agreement, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 53)
- International Studies, Mario Einaudi Center for, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 54)
- International Studies, Mario Einaudi Center for, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 55)
- International Studies, Mario Einaudi Center for, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 56)
- International Studies, Mario Einaudi Center for, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 57)
- J (General Correspondence), 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 58)
- K (General Correspondence), 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 59)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 60)
- Kellogg Foundation--Professions Education Initiative, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 61)
- Kraft General Foods, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- L (General Correspondence), 1992-1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Landscape Architecture Program, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Landscape Architecture Program--Reaccreditation, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory--Advisory Council, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- M (General Correspondence), 1992-1995 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Mann Library, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Media Services, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Microbiology, Section of, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Miner Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Minority Resources Development Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Northeast Cooperative Council, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 18)